=The Outlaw=
(This story is entirely fictional.)
(All settings are imaginary.)
=Episode 5=
Sihan!
Sihan! Are you okay?
Why'd you
call me back?
Your father says
to stay away from drugs.
I haven't.
Stay out of Suowen's business too.
Once you get involved,
it's hard to get out.
Please.
You really think you're my mom?
The mine is your father's lifelong work.
You can't destroy it.
Okay.
Take it easy.
I'll do as you say.
Happy now?
Your father's still alive.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
Sooner or later, you'll be mine.
Hey,
piggy.
You're so clever.
You actually tried to talk my stepmom
into luring me away.
Come on.
She's my stepmom.
Why would she help you
take me down?
Zhou Yan...
I was wrong.
I should've...
I should've listened to you.
I just wanted to make money on my own.
I fell for his trap.
I want to go home.
Okay.
I'll take you home.
Home?
Hey!
Then how would you get such good stuff?
Come on.
Hey.
You mess with me,
and this is what happens.
Zhou Yan.
Go ahead, get mad.
The madder you get,
the more excited I get.
Zhou Yan!
Hey.
Don't you like this?
Here.
Have some more.
Come on, have a little more.
Sihan!
Come on.
You dare waste my stash?
Don't you like it?
Come here. Have all you want.
Sihan!
Nice part.
Zhou Yan!
Zhou Yan, I did love you,
but you can't afford the future I want.
If we stay together,
you'll destroy yourself completely.
Yan...
Maybe you should get another job.
Keep doing this,
and your body will give out first..
Oh. I'm fine.
Sparring pays well.
Six more months,
and I'll have enough
for the diamond ring you want.
I'm not worth that ring.
All I can do
is let you go.
Don't...
Don't let go.
Let's start over.
I saw how hard you were working.
So I came to Langia
with my best friend to make money.
But we never thought we'd get tricked
into body packing.
They forced me to use drugs.
I can't face you anymore.
Staying with you
will only drag you down.
Getting all lovey-dovey, huh?
I'll make sure you don't last long.
Stop hitting him!
Zhou Yan...
Forget about me.
Sihan!
Officer.
This guy from Huaguo
killed and robbed people here.
They all saw it.
They can prove it.
Speak up!
Yes. We all saw it.
A criminal like him...
Officer, you can't let him go.
Of course not.
Take him away.
Natuo!
This ends with one of us dead!
See you.
Yan was definitely set up.
Dad.
(Mokun, Police Chief)
That Huaguo man, Zhou Yan,
came to Langia
to find his girlfriend, Lin Sihan.
There's no way he'd kill her.
Please conduct the investigation again.
Got it.
But now there are witnesses
and physical evidence.
It's goinig to be tough.
Zhou Yan offended Natuo
at the jade appraisal event.
Natuo must've deliberately set him up.
Oh.
So it's him.
All right.
I
understand.
Mona,
come back to the station.
It's too dangerous out here alone.
Dashan, Suowen, and Natuo...
I've mapped out
their criminal network.
Once we arrest them,
we can definitely get to Mian,
who's behind them.
This evidence
is nowhere near enough.
Do you know
how many higher-ups are protecting them?
Then I'll find more evidence.
Mona.
I know
you want to avenge your mom.
But Mian isn't someone you can take on.
Leave this to me.
Dad.
I've waited for years.
And what have you found?
Dashan, Suowen, and Natuo...
The police won't even touch them.
Zhou Yan is the only one
who dares take on the Big Three.
So I've made up my mind.
I'll use Zhou Yan as my way in.
I'll expose Mian myself
and get justice for Mom.
I only ask one thing.
Keep Zhou Yan alive.
(Zhou Yan, I did love you,)
(but you can't afford)
(the future I want.)
(If we stay together,)
(you'll destroy yourself completely.)
(All I can do)
(is let you go.)
(Forget me.)
Wait.
Someone wants to see you.
Hey, piggy.
Long time no see.
Look at you now. What a pathetic mess.
Weren't you so tough?
Your girlfriend's dead.
I know you're heartbroken.
I'm heartbroken too.
It took a lot of work
to get her body
out of police custody.
Look.
Know what this is?
Her ashes!
- Want them?
- Give them to me!
Come on. Come get them.
Give them to me!
Come on! Come get them!
Look.
Lin Sihan's everywhere now.
I'll kill you!
Didn't you say
this ends with one of us dead?
Come on. Come at me.
Too bad.
Wu Suowen won't give you the chance.
He's waiting for your heart
to save his life.
(Last night,)
(rioting and vandalism broke out
on Langia's Old Street.)
(The gang behind it claimed)
(it was acting on Mian's orders.)
(So far, no one in Langia)
(has stepped forward to restore order.)
Hey, kid.
You owe our boss something.
You're...
one of Suowen's people?
Go.
The new guy
didn't know what he was doing.
He slipped and fell on a blade.
Think that story will work?
You know who's really to blame.
Don't go after the wrong guy down there.
Then go see him yourself.
Don't kill me!
- I was wrong!
- Hit him!
I was wrong!
Let him go!
Move!
Back off!
Get out of the way!
You again?
(Solitary Confinement)
(Last night,)
(rioting broke out
on Langia's Old Street.)
(The gang responsible claimed)
(they were acting on orders
from Old Mian.)
(So far, no one in Langia)
(has stepped forward to restore orders.)
(Mian.)
(The King of Langia.)
(My idol.)
(But no one's ever seen
what he looks like.)
(All anyone knows is he has a dahlia
on his chest.)
(Too bad.)
(He vanished three years ago.)
(Your girlfriend's dead.)
(I'm heartbroken too.)
(Look. Know what this is?)
(Her ashes!)
(Do it right.)
(Handle my heart carefully.)
(Don't you know? Here in Langia,)
(this...)
(and this...)
(are all worth a lot of money.)
(Take him upstairs.)
Go.
Let that kid
out of solitary.
♪Dust rises along the border♪
♪Out here, life and death are routine♪
♪Spent shells fall, last echoes ring♪
♪Friends yesterday, now in battle♪
♪Fate's blade falls, who can stop it?♪
♪Against the tide, I never bow♪
♪The night is long, the road unclear♪
♪My life is mine to bear♪
♪In chaos, a bloodied titan rages♪
♪I crush the thorns and reach the dawn♪
♪I fight back from death on all fronts♪
♪My fate is mine to command♪
♪Who dares stand in my way?♪
♪I weave through storms of bullets♪
♪I fight through flashing blades♪
♪Blood stains the whole land red♪
♪The bonds we forged stay in my heart♪
♪Plots and schemes are everywhere♪
♪Deceit runs deep, hard to see through♪
♪Every step is planned. I won't retreat♪
♪A spark ignites in the dark♪
♪So what if fate mocks me?♪
♪This fight will defy fate itself♪
♪Break every shackle, break every lock♪
♪Anger burns inside my chest♪
♪With blood and sweat♪
♪I forge my glory♪
♪In this world of chaos♪
♪I carve out a road to brighter days♪
♪My legend♪
♪I'll write every chapter myself♪
♪In chaos, a bloodied titan rages♪
♪I crush the thorns and reach the dawn♪
♪I fight back from death on all fronts♪
♪My fate is mine to command♪
♪Who dares stand in my way?♪